Samantha Wanamaker

Projects

Information Architecture Redesign

March 2020-June 2020

Researched and identified problems in the mobile web navigation of the Legal Aid Society of San Diego. Performed content inventory, card sorting, treejack testing, and chalkmark testing to create a new navigational system.

Cloud9

March 2020-June 2020

Exploratory research project that aims to understand user's need for a technology-based solution to help them store, organize, and distribute digital assets post-mortem.

Performed observations, interview, and surveys. Used findings to support implications of features Cloud9 would need to be viable to users.

coLab

September 2019-November 2019

Redesign of D2L (Desire to Learn) platform to be more inclusive of group communication and work. Created wireframes, storyboards, personas, and prototypes. Performed iterative usability testing.

Experience

English Tutor | Cafetalk

August 2020-Current

Teaching English learners in Japan online. Help them improve on their pronunciation, grammar, and general conversation fluency.

Autism Specialist | Alternative Teaching Strategy Center

October 2018-July 2020

Worked one on one session with autistic students. Used visual learning styles to help them comprehend concepts. Taught subjects in math, biology, language arts, science, and typing.

www.sswanamaker.github.io sswanamaker07@gmail.com (619) 597-9474

www.linkedin.com/in/sswanamaker

Education

DePaul University

June 2018-Current

M.S. Human Computer Interaction

University of California, Davis

September 2014—June 2018 B.S. Psychology, Biology Emphasis Minor History

Skills

Information Architecture

Usability Testing

Content Inventory

User Research

Wireframing

Prototyping

Personas

Storyboarding

Tools

Axure

Figma

Illustrator

HTML/CSS

Qualtrics

Optimal Workshop